[ Watch on KissFlix.co ]
It all began, freshmen year of high school.
[Year 1, Class 2]
You broke up with your girlfriend, Serizawa?
Why? She seemed like a nice girl.
She was, but...
Same reason as always, huh?
I never really understood what it meant to romantically "like" someone.
Morning.
Morning!
I liked chatting with people.
And I liked that others liked me.
- I'm feeling eh. - Aw, too bad.
- See you! - Later.
But...
I never felt the desire
to reach out to someone myself.
[Indoor voices - Library Committee]
Long story short,
your indifference made the girl anxious,
and before you knew it, she self-destructed.
I'm seriously the worst.
Don't blame yourself too hard.
You can't choose who you love.
I know that, but still...
If you're going to mope,
do your job.
[Returns] [Borrowing]
Yes, sir.
That was when I met him.
A boy I didn't know was engrossed in a book.
That's all it was.
But for some reason, I couldn't take my eyes off of him.
My heart was set ablaze.
It was an emotion I'd never experienced before.
[Episode 7]
Great timing, Serizawa.
- Could you handle those... - Yes, sir!
My interest for him grew by the day.
Rock paper scissors, shoot!
And shoot!
Look over there!
- Score! - Aw, man.
Let's just call it your win.
Serizawa, you're helping at the library again?
- Yeah. - Seriously? Any reason why?
Well, you know.
Huh?
Suzuki. Let's head home together.
Yeah.
I'm beat.
Same.
So, his name is Suzuki.
Suzuki, Suzuki... [Returns]
Huh? He's not listed.
He doesn't borrow out any books?
Then what is he always so excited to read?
What're you looking at?
Nothing.
I'm just glad you're motivated.
What is he reading?
I'm yakisoba bread, all the way.
Really?
Red bean bread is great, too.
What is he reading?
If it were anyone else, I could just ask. But not Suzuki.
What's he up to?
Join the judo team.
Why?
To make the most of our youth!
Want me to sign up?
- For real? - You're serious?
Just kidding.
- And you? - I'll throw you.
Amateur.
Yeah?
Serizawa?
Hello?
Earth to Serizawa?
- Maybe he's serious now. - You think?
Wait, he turned in.
- I'll take this. - Thank you.
[Tatakiwari Ishibashi's works]
[Moon in the Deep Sea]
BL?
I want you to look at me.
Our relationship will be changed forever.
I want to really know you.
If you get any closer, we can't go back.
I don't want to.
I'm fine with our relationship changing.
- I can't hold back anymore. - Neither can I.
What the heck?
This is so exhilarating.
Huh? Hold on.
Is this why Suzuki looked like that?
Seriously?
No way.
That's so cute.
"Cute".
Once I verbalized it, I couldn't stop myself.
Cute.
Are you okay?
Yeah. I just dropped the eraser.
Let me help.
Thanks.
I want to know more about him.
I want to get closer to him.
Cute.
Suzuki. You got some on your mouth.
There.
Thanks.
More.
At some point, I had become
hopelessly obsessed with Suzuki.
And yet...
I was afraid talking to him would scare him away.
Suzuki! Morning.
- Morning. - Let's go.
Yeah.
You look tired. Up late doing homework?
- We had homework? - Yeah.
Really?
The days passed without ever reaching out to him.
Near the end of freshman year...
I'm starving.
- What're you getting? - Curry bread.
- Again? - Seriously?
Suzuki began to spend more time alone.
Huh? BL?
Like, boys' love?
I get it now.
Of course not. That's just gross.
Did you do it?
Did not!
It's so awkward with Suzuki now.
Yeah, seriously.
He's always absorbed in his BL.
And his face!
- He gets so red! - Yeah, ew!
You guys, knock it off.
- What? - Why?
You said it yourself that BL was gross.
- Yeah, you agreed with us. - Well, I...
Hey.
I heard something about BL.
Mind if I join in?
I'm also a BL fan.
- Let's go. - Yeah.
Pathetic.
Suzuki.
What did those guys say to you?
Were you frustrated?
Were you hurt?
Frankly, I was pissed off.
Not only at the people who hurt you,
but at myself, for not being able
to protect you.
What's up, Serizawa?
I thought we had dinner plans today.
Sorry.
Could I ask you guys a question?
If I said I liked BL, how would you all react?
Huh? That's a random question.
If you like BL, so what? We wouldn't care.
Right?
Yeah.
More importantly, I'm starving.
I knew it.
People like you guys exist, so why do others have to hurt him?
Something happened, didn't it?
What's up? We'll listen.
Here, have some chocolate.
It'll help.
Okay, I've decided.
I'm going to become his friend.
Huh?
I won't scare him.
I'll approach him slowly.
And when I become his bestest friend, he can talk all about his hobby with me.
What's he going on about?
But first things first, I need to brush up on my BL.
Dude, you good?
I'm going to become the King of BL!
What?
Sophomore year began.
Please put us in the same class.
I'll be back soon.
I'm with you chumps, again?
Aw, come on. [Year 2, Class 1]
We know you're happy!
Am not.
Score!
I sent a "thank you" to the BL gods.
[Hajime Suzuki]
Suzuki, you dropped this.
Here.
Th-Thanks.
That being said...
Bowling or karaoke?
- What's the move? - I say the gym!
- Denied. - Overruled.
- Not happening. - What about you, Serizawa?
Hey, there's a party room available!
Seriously?
Do they have weights there?
Y-Yeah. I think so.
Hey, good for you, Iwasaki!
Suzuki.
We're going out as a class after this.
Wanna join?
Sorry.
I'm not good with social events.
No worries. Sorry to put you on the spot.
Let's go again some other time.
I couldn't close the gap between us so easily.
[Idea Journal]
A journal?
That day, I was given a miracle.
[Haruto Serizawa]
You write about a "Haruto Serizawa" in here.
Is that supposed to be me?
And then...
Give me the honor
of being your first reader.
After discovering Suzuki's secret, I became his very first reader.
Then, I became his friend.
Eventually, we went on a date.
Suzuki. Look at me.
And finally, we kissed.
Now, back to present day.
I'm sorry!
I can't go on a date with you.
Why not?
I...
I already know
what this feeling is.
I have someone I like.
Suzuki.
Serizawa.
When I call out to him, he greets me with a smile.
But...
That's still not enough.
What're you reading?
A manga I bought yesterday.
Look, isn't this bottom way too dense?
Huh? Why?
See, look.
The top's clearly obsessed with him,
but the bottom totally doesn't notice.
You're right.
That's cute.
Hopefully, he catches on soon.
The first person I ever fell for.
Let's get going.
No.
- Serizawa? - No.
No, no, no!
We have to leave eventually.
I don't intend on letting him get away.
No.
Let's make summer memories together, Suzuki.
I do have someone I like.
They're cute, kind, and hardworking.
Know who I'm talking about?
All right, ready?
There is someone who meets all those conditions.